stronglifts.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | StrongLifts

The StrongLifts Privacy Policy helps you understand how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and helps you make make informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. StrongLifts.com is a service offered by StrongLifts Limited (“StrongLifts”) and references in this document to “us,” “our,” and “we” refer to StrongLifts.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  
When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the site.

You will provide us information about yourself when you register for email newsletters, install and use our mobile apps and purchase any StrongLifts product or services. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

Similar to other commercial websites, this site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how this site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at this site, and the websites visited just before and just after our site. We may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which email users read and how they responded to them.

HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?  
We use personal information to improve our website, products and apps. We also use it to provide customer service. We may use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email. When you unsubscribe, we delete that email from our database and don’t contact it again unless you later decide to register again.

WHAT ARE COOKIES?  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site.

HOW DO WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM COOKIES?  
As you use this website, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting this site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve this site and better serve you. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES  
The information we collect is used to improve the content of this site and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes. We do use third parties to host the website, send emails, process payments and so on. These third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with our business activities only. No third party will abuse your personal information. For example: the third party we use to send emails, will not use your personal information to send you emails unrelated to us. We hate spam more than you and we don’t want to be part of it. Your personal information is safe with us.

NOTICE OF NEW SERVICES AND CHANGES  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You can always notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email. When you unsubscribe, we delete that email from our database and don’t contact it again unless you later decide to register again.

HOW DO WE SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?  
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on this site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.

WHAT ABOUT OTHER WEBSITES LINKED TO THIS SITE?  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

YOUR CONSENT  
By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
